Guide to the Daniel Nilva Negatives PHOTOS.067
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Unions., 90011
  - Subseries I:CC: United Textile Workers of America., 90012
    - Local 229 Christmas Party, Regional Office, 129 Lexington, Dec 21, 1957; 90013 (Box 1, Item 718)
- Series II: Labor Organizations., 89935
  - Subseries II:A: American Federation of Labor., 90005
    - AFL Convention Atlantic City, 1935; 90010 (Box 4, Item 97)
    - [Broadcast] 58th St. Studio [at A.B.C. Studio], May 29, 1947; 90009 (Box 2, Item 883)
    - Broadcast; 58th St. Studio, May 29, 1947; 90008 (Box 1, Item 53)
    - Statler-NY [Appears to be have been shot at the AFL-CIO merger convention at the Statler-Hilton Hotel in New York City. Includes numerous union leaders (negative 686-30 shows David Dubinsky, for example).], Dec 1, 1955; 90007 (Box 4, Item 686)
    - AFL convention (1--13) 12-1 (1--12) 12-2, Dec 1, 1955-Dec 2, 1955; 90006 (Box 2, Item 884)
    - United Garment Workers of America Nashville Convention, 1914 (Box 6, Item 12058)
      Historical Note
      United Garment Workers of America union was affiliated with the American Federal Labor.
  - Subseries II:B: American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO)., 89997
    - Meeting, Commodore Hotel, Jun 8, 1950; 90004 (Box 2, Item 885)
    - United Labor Commission, AFL-CIO Election UJZ TV, Nov 3, 1952; 90003 (Box 4, Item 687)
    - AFL-CIO Convention 1st Day; Labor Daily AFL- CIO Convention 2nd Day; AFL-CIO Convention 3rd Day; AFL-CIO Convention 4th Day; Radio Liberator; End Empty Hall; Unity Convention Eleanor Roosevelt; Puerto Rican Delegates; City of Hope, Zimmerman and Williams; Kenosha[?] Labor K, Att. Harold J. Newton, Dec 5, 1955-Dec 8, 1955; 90002 (Box 2, Item 886)
    - AFL-CIO Convention [Speakers include: Eleanor Roosevelt, George Meany], Dec 7, 1966-Dec 8, 1966; 90001 (Box 4, Item 688)
    - AFL-CIO Unemployment Office, Jun 25, 1958; 90000 (Box 2, Item 887)
    - AFL-CIO Meeting Manhattan Hotel on Behalf of G.E. Strike, IUE District 4[?], Oct 19, 1960; 89999 (Box 2, Item 888)
    - AFL-CIO Eastern Region Education Conference Shelbourne Hotel, Apr 25, 1961; 89998 (Box 2, Item 890)
  - Subseries II:C: American Commission on Africa., 89995
    - American Commission on Africa: Arrival of Students, Sep 10, 1959; 89996 (Box 4, Item 683)
  - Subseries II:D: American Labor Education Service., 89993
    - Eleanor Roosevelt, American Labor Education Service; E.R. Addressing Lucilee Conn, Chairman of Board, Hotel Shelbourne, Nov 14, 1955; 89994 (Box 2, Item 947)
  - Subseries II:E: Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO)., 89986
    - [Meeting in an auditorium or hotel ballroom, mainly speakers shown. Banners include legend, "CIO" and slogans "Organize the Unorganized White Collar Worker" "Hail the work of the CIO."], [1930s?]; 89992 (Box 1, Item 586)
    - Furniture Salesmen, CIO Local 853, [1950s?]; 89991 (Box 2, Item 892)
    - CIO Steel Hearings, [1950s?]; 89990 (Box 2, Item 893)
    - CIO Convention, 1951; 89989 (Box 1, Item 719)
    - [CIO Convention, Hotel Commodore, New York City. Includes Michael Quill and Philip Murray.], Nov 1, 1951; 89988 (Box 2, Item 950)
    - CIO Convention, NYC, Nov 5, 1951-Nov 11, 1951; 89987 (Box 2, Item 889)
  - Subseries II:F: Harlem Labor Center., 89983
    - [Harlem Labor Center meeting], [1950s?]; 89985 (Box 2, Item 894)
    - [Meeting; Includes door labeled "Painters DC 9." Mostly African-American audience. Harlem Labor Center?], [1950s?]; 89984 (Box 2, Item 895)
  - Subseries II:G: Histadrut., 89965
    - Histadrut Luncheon, Hotel Astor, [1950s?]; 89982 (Box 2, Item 912)
    - Histadrut Meeting, Hotel Astor, Dec 6, 1956; 89981 (Box 2, Item 896)
    - Histadrut, City Hall, Apr 4, 1957; 89980 (Box 2, Item 897)
    - Histadrut Luncheon for Moshe Bartal; Histadrut Representative to U.S.; Kruzo [Pincus Caruso], Paole Zion; J. Schlossberg; Sarah Surchin, Pioneer Women; Cecil Human, Isr. Con.; Moshe Bartal, Histadrut; Dr. Begun, Chairman; J. Breslan; I. Nagler; Eddie Euro; I. H. Goldberg, Hatters, May 10, 1957; 89979 (Box 2, Item 898)
    - Histadrut Dinner, Sheraton Astor, Sep 18, 1957; 89978 (Box 2, Item 900)
    - Histadrut, Phil Murray Luncheon, Commodore, Sep 24, 1957; 89977 (Box 2, Item 901)
    - Histadrut, J. Avidor [sp?], Israeli Ambassador to USSR, and Wife, Oct 10, 1957; 89976 (Box 2, Item 902)
    - Histadrut Conference, Commodore Hotel, Oct 27, 1957; 89975 (Box 2, Item 903)
    - Histadrut, Israeli Entertainers, Josefa Schocken, Shimon Finkel, Nov 19, 1957; 89974 (Box 2, Item 904)
    - Histadrut, Bessarabian [?] Committee, Hist. Hqtrs., Jan 2, 1958; 89973 (Box 2, Item 905)
    - Histadrut, [Annual] Service Luncheon, Park Plaza, Jan 6, 1958; 89972 (Box 2, Item 906)
    - Histadrut, Picker Equipment, Jan 10, 1958; 89971 (Box 2, Item 907)
    - Histadrut, Luncheon, Astor Hotel, Jan 16, 1958; 89970 (Box 2, Item 908)
    - Histadrut, Branch 400, Feb 1, 1958; 89969 (Box 2, Item 909)
    - Histadrut, District 65 Contribution, Oct 28, 1958; 89968 (Box 2, Item 910)
    - Histadrut, Books for Israel, Marty Cohn Donor, Dec 2, 1958; 89967 (Box 2, Item 911)
    - Histadrut, Check from Local 10, May 16, 1975; 89966 (Box 2, Item 899)
  - Subseries II:H: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions., 89962
    - Free Trade Union Committee, ICFTU Luncheon: Francis, Edward, Tachin, Merison, Lovestone, Zimmerman; J. McLarin, Sleeping Car Porters; Noah Walters, Workmans Comp.; Maida Springer, Local 22 Laundry Workers; Ed Welsh, Rubber Workers; Louis Nelson, Local 155; Charles Zimmerman, Local 22; Gilbert and Jonas (Information Associates), [1960s?]; 89963 (Box 2, Item 913)
  - Subseries II:I: International Workers Front Against War., 89959
    - International Workers Front against War Convention, Oct 1, 1939; 89961 (Box 4, Item 78)
    - [International Workers Front against War (possibly affiliated with Communist Party Opposition), Meeting at Marxist Center. Diego Rivera murals are visible on the walls in the background.], ca.1939; 89960 (Box 2, Item 914)
  - Subseries II:J: Jewish Labor Committee (JLC)., 89943
    - Jewish Labor Council [Jewish Labor Committee?] Luncheon, Astor, Feb 12, 1949; 89958 (Box 1, Item 68)
    - Jewish Labor Committee: [Meeting or conference (possibly on the topic of discrimination in housing and education) held at a resort (probably the ILGWU's Unity House)., [1950s?]; 89957 (Box 1, Item 720)
    - JLC Mural Presented to Workmen's Circle, [1950s?]; 89956 (Box 2, Item 926)
    - Ceil Chapman, JLC, 530 7th Ave [Group photograph of workers in a shop and a meeting in an office. Ceil Chapman was a women's clothing designer. Perhaps this was her workshop and perhaps she is pictured in the meeting in the office.], Apr 27, 1950; 89955 (Box 2, Item 915)
    - Jewish Labor Committee, Mayor Wagner Swearing in, Charles Zimmerman, City Hall, Jan 19, 1955; 89954 (Box 2, Item 916)
    - JLC, [Photograph of a painting of B. Charney Vladeck speaking], Oct 27, 1955; 89953 (Box 2, Item 917)
    - Rand School [Conference called by the National Trade Union Committee for Racial Justice on the problems of African-American workers; at the Rand School, 7 East 15th Street, New York City], Nov 11, 1955; 89952 (Box 3, Item 1072)
    - Jewish Labor Committee, AFL-CIO Convention: Averell Harriman and Charles Zimmerman. [Also, Zimmerman with Adlai Stevenson; Gov. G. Menner Williams. In all four shots the men are posed in front of a sign that reads: "United House of Labor."], Dec 6, 1955; 89951 (Box 2, Item 918)
    - Jewish Labor Committee, Weekend Conference [National Trade Union Conference on Civil Rights], Belmont Plaza, May 4, 1956-May 6, 1956; 89950 (Box 2, Item 919)
    - Jewish Labor Committee: Hungarian Protest Meeting [Madison Square Garden], Averell Harriman [In shot #9, additional caption reads, "Pat and Schnitzler." "Pat" probably refers to JLC's Jacob Pat.], Nov 8, 1956; 89949 (Box 2, Item 920)
    - Jewish Labor Committee Emergency Conference, Belmont Plaza, Nov 30, 1956; 89948 (Box 2, Item 921)
    - Jewish Labor Committee [at?] (Housing Meeting), [AFSCME, Local 1707], Jun 23, 1958; 89947 (Box 2, Item 922)
    - Jewish Labor Committee, William Green Plaque, Feb 5, 1959; 89946 (Box 2, Item 923)
    - JLC, [Dedication of William Green Human Relations Library], Apr 20, 1959; 89945 (Box 2, Item 924)
    - Jewish Labor Committee, Mayor's Office, Apr 17, 1961; 89944 (Box 2, Item 925)
  - Subseries II:K: League for Industrial Democracy., 89940
    - Student League for Industrial Democracy; [Meeting or lecture in auditorium; group portrait shot at a branch of the Workmen's Circle.], Dec 27, 1946; 89942 (Box 1, Item 67)
    - Luncheon Awards to Luis Munoz Marin, of Puerto Rico, Apr 13, 1957; 89941 (Box 2, Item 929)
  - Subseries II:L: New York City Central Labor Council., 89938
    - Central Trades Council Rump Meeting for Judge Ferdinand Pecora, McAlpin [Hotel], [Oct 27, 1950?]; 89939 (Box 1, Item 651)
  - Subseries II:M: Women's Trade Union League., 89936
    - WTUL [Women's Trade Union League], Scholarships, Jun 11, 1957; 89937 (Box 2, Item 931)
- Series III: Political Parties and Organizations., 89919
  - Subseries III:A: American Labor Party., 89930
    - La Guardia [Madison Square Garden] [Signs/banners include slogans: American Labor Party/Re-elect La Guardia], [1938?]; 89934 (Box 1, Item 555)
    - American Labor Party (Top Officials): [Alex] Rose, Jacob Potofsky, Luigi Antonini, Louis Hollander, Andrew Armstrong, C. Strebel, 1936; 89933 (Box 4, Item 236)
    - American Labor Party, Madison Square Garden Meeting, 1936; 89932 (Box 4, Item 89)
    - American Labor Party, Roosevelt, Wallace and Mead, [1940s?]; 89931 (Box 1, Item 69)
  - Subseries III:B: British Labour Party., 89928
    - British Labour Party, Herbert Morrison, [1960s?]; 89929 (Box 1, Item 725)
  - Subseries III:C: Independent Communist Labor League., 89922
    - [Independent Communist Labor League], Meetings and Personalities [6th National Convention, Communist Party Opposition], [1930s?]; 89926 (Box 4, Item 222)
    - [Communist Party Opposition], Convention: Labor Day Weekend, Sep 1, 1935; 89925 (Box 4, Item 220)
    - [Communist Party Opposition], Washington's Birthday Weekend, Feb 1936; 89924 (Box 4, Item 219)
    - [Communist Party Opposition, 6th National Convention], 1936; 89927 (Box 1, Item 584)
    - [Independent Communist Labor League] 1937 National Convention of the ICLL or 1938 National Convention of the ICLL, or the 1938 New York District meeting of the ICLL., 1937, 1938; 487311 (Box 4, Item 12052)
    - [Independent Communist Labor League], 7th National Convention, New York City, ICLL Headquarters, 131 W. 33rd St.; District 65, Textile Workers, AFSCME 1717 [Signs include: "Hail Iberian Communist Youth," "P.O.U.M." (Workers Party of Marxist Unification) [Copy shot of document in German, Spanish and French, dated November 1939, translated: "Platform of International Workers Front Against War"], Jul 4, 1938; 89923 (Box 4, Item 641)
    - [Independent Communist Labor League] ICLL Meetings and Personalities, [1940s?]; 89964 (Box 4, Item 223)
  - Subseries III:D: Liberal Party., 89920
    - Liberal Party, undated; 89921 (Box 4, Item 542)
- Series IV: Demonstrations., 89885
  - [May Day Parade, 30-34th St. and 8th Ave.; "Bronx County Committee Communist Party"; [Signs: "Join the Communist Party Opposition USA"; "The CIO made Morgan Settle"; "Down with Imperialist War!"; "Free Mooney and Billings"; "Hail International Brigade"; "Support Anti-Lynching Bill"; "Workers School"; "Unity"; "Lincoln Battalion... Fighting in Spain."], [1930s?]; 89918 (Box 1, Item 596)
  - [Parade at Union Square. 1937?][Signs: "The Union for All Office Workers Join the BS&AU" (Bookkeepers Stenographers, and Accountants Union); "Communist Party Opposition"; "Communist Party of New York State Workers of the World Unite!"], [1930s?]; 89917 (Box 1, Item 594)
  - [Mass meeting in a stadium or large indoor auditorium; sign: "Federation German Workers Clubs of Greater New York--Hitler is Not Germany."], [1930s?]; 89916 (Box 1, Item 590)
  - [Anti-William Randolph Hearst banner at a parade (perhaps May Day?): "Keep Hearst Out of Schools], [1930s?]; 89915 (Box 1, Item 589)
  - [Speaker; banner: (Oppose the?) (Internati?)onal fascist offensive"], [1930s?]; 89914 (Box 1, Item 588)
  - [Anti-Fascist convention; in background a banner/sign showing image of man wrenching swastika. Microphones show the speeches are being broadcast on radio station WEVD.], [1930s?]; 89913 (Box 1, Item 587)
  - [Unlabeled. Street gathering? protest? demonstration?], [1930s?]; 89912 (Box 4, Item 228)
  - Austrian Demonstration, 1934; 89911 (Box 1, Item 40)
  - May Day, 1934; 89910 (Box 1, Item 42)
  - May Day parade, 1935, New York City., 487310 (Box 4, Item 12051)
  - May Day, May 1, 1936; 89909 (Box 4, Item 85)
  - May Day, May 1, 1937; 89908 (Box 4, Item 86)
  - Ford Demonstration, Dec 24, 1937; 89907 (Box 4, Item 106)
  - May Day, May 1, 1938; 89906 (Box 4, Item 87)
  - Czech Demonstration, Columbus Circle/C.P.M., Mar 5, 1939; 89905 (Box 4, Item 600)
  - Charles Zimmerman [Two identical copy shots of an unidentified demonstration], [1940s?]; 89904 (Box 2, Item 1003)
  - May Day, [1940s?]; 89903 (Box 4, Item 696)
  - [Labor Demonstration, includes sign: "This is What We Demand for Xmas"], [1940s?]; 89902 (Box 1, Item 585)
  - May Day, [1940s?]; 89901 (Box 4, Item 98)
  - May Day, [1940?]; 89900 (Box 4, Item 105)
  - May Day, [1940s?]; 89899 (Box 4, Item 212)
  - San Francisco, Waterfront fight started when some members of the AFL Sailors Union of the Pacific Coast fought their way through a picket line established by the CIO Ship Scalers and Painters Union., Oct 15, 1940; 89898 (Box not specified, Item 549)
  - [Dressmakers Demonstration], [1950s?]; 89897 (Box 4, Item 691)
  - [Local 1-S DSWU--RWDSU May's Protest], [1950s?]; 89896 (Box 4, Item 698)
  - Civil Rights Rally [Madison Square Garden] Celeb., May 24, 1956; 89895 (Box 4, Item 690)
  - Labor Day, Sep 1, 1959; 89894 (Box 1, Item 721)
  - Labor Day, Sep 1, 1959; 89893 (Box 4, Item 693)
  - Pickets: South African Embassy [Anti-Apartheid Protest], Mar 30, 1960; 89892 (Box 4, Item 697)
  - Labor Day, Sep 5, 1960; 89891 (Box 4, Item 694)
  - Labor Day, S.I.U., Sep 5, 1960; 89890 (Box 1, Item 722)
  - Kennedy Rally: Garment District, Oct 27, 1960; 89889 (Box 4, Item 692)
  - District 65 Kennedy Rally: Garment District, Oct 27, 1960; 89888 (Box 2, Item 934)
  - [Labor Day], Sep 1, 1961; 89887 (Box 4, Item 695)
  - Labor Day, Sep 1, 1961; 89886 (Box 1, Item 723)
- Series V: Strikes., 89872
  - [Copy shot] Trolley Strike, 1886; 89884 (Box 2, Item 936)
  - [Copy shots of:] Labor/Seaman's Strike? England/Lining up for Strike Benefits, [1930s?]; 89883 (Box 1, Item 553)
  - [Copy shots of:] Strike: 11/24/36 "We are prepared to fight to the finish"; "Protesting imprisonment of 7 seamen convicted of possessing dynamite during tanker strike 20 months earlier. Building is San Francisco Standard Oil"; 11/18/36 Strike bound S.S. Washington sails. Picketing US lines; Picketing Matson Piers, San Francisco 11/5/36; San Francisco "Three a Day" 12/7/36; Began May 9, 1936, 89882 (Box 1, Item 497)
  - Strikes: International Seafarers Union Members on Strike, 1936; 89881 (Box 1, Item 66)
  - [Copy shots of:] Strike: Houston, Texas; Wilbur Dickey Dumped, Dickey Patrolman M.F.O.W., 1936; 89880 (Box 1, Item 50)
  - Strike: Meeting in Lyceum Hall, 1936; 89879 (Box 1, Item 49)
  - [Copy shots of:] Union Square mass meeting of waterfront workers 12/12/36 Strike began October 29, 1936, 89878 (Box 1, Item 48)
  - Registering for Picket Duty, 1936; 89877 (Box 1, Item 41)
  - Lang News Strike, [1940s?]; 89876 (Box 4, Item 601)
  - Met News Strike, [1940s?]; 89875 (Box 4, Item 215)
  - Cohn Hall Marx Strike, [1940s?]; 89874 (Box 4, Item 213)
  - Strike?: Roosevelt Home Hyde Park, NY, [1950s?]; 89873 (Box 2, Item 938)
- Series VI: Miscellaneous Events., 89862
  - [Unlabeled Convention], [1930s?]; 89871 (Box 1, Item 593)
  - [An unidentified man (almost certainly New York City Mayor Fiorello LaGuardia) speaking at a podium at mass meeting or convention, his speech being broadcast on radio stations WEVD and WMCA; also, General Hugh Johnson], [1930s?]; 89870 (Box 1, Item 591)
  - Welcome to Soviet North Pole [Air] Flyers [Sign: "Soviet Pioneers of the Air"], [1930s?]; 89869 (Box 4, Item 702)
  - Banquet for Bob Edwards, Jun 23, 1938; 89868 (Box 4, Item 216)
  - Gen. Eisenhower Museum of Art, Apr 1, 1946; 89867 (Box 4, Item 644)
  - Hyde Park ,Roosevelt, Sep 7, 1946; 89866 (Box 1, Item 498)
  - Delegation to Hyde Park -- Eleanor Roosevelt, [1950s?]; 89865 (Box 1, Item 724)
  - Cora Bacor, Winner of UN Essay Contest Mayor Wagner, Eleanor Roosevelt, Oct 24, 1957; 89864 (Box 2, Item 928)
  - News Alliance Capitol Funeral, May 6, 1958; 89863 (Box 4, Item 701)
  - Haym Salomon Home Annual Meeting, 1970 (Box 6, Item 12053)
  - Unidentified speaker addressing a crowd of spectators at an outdoor meeting, undated (Box 6, Item 12054, Item 12055, Item 12056)
  - Miscellaneous Events (Box 8)
- Series VII: Personalities., 89770
  - Alsop[?], J. H.S., [Oct 1946?]; 89861 (Box 1, Item 556)
  - Murray Baron [?], Dec 9, 1958; 89860 (Box 2, Item 951)
  - Gus Beam; R. Elber[?], [1950s?]; 89859 (Box 2, Item 952)
  - Max Bloom, Oct 18, 1950; 89858 (Box 2, Item 953)
  - Mel Bloom, May 15, 1956; 89857 (Box 2, Item 954)
  - Boklaw [?] Family, Aug 5, 1951; 89856 (Box 2, Item 955)
  - Burton [Burtan?] Family, Sep 19, 1953; 89855 (Box 1, Item 726)
  - Val Burtan, Sep 24, 1958; 89854 (Box 2, Item 956)
  - Burtan, V.G. [Val Burtan?], Oct 1, 1961; 89853 (Box 2, Item 957)
  - CIO James Carey, Jun 1, 1950; 89852 (Box 2, Item 958)
  - David L. Cole [Director of Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service], [1950s?]; 89851 (Box 2, Item 959)
  - Lara Colombia T.U. Head [Meeting (luncheon?) in a small conference room], 1950; 89850 (Box 2, Item 1004)
  - Ely Culbertson [speaking at a dinner], 1946; 89849 (Box 1, Item 47)
  - Lester Davis, [1960s?]; 89848 (Box 1, Item 727)
  - Linda DeDefler [sp?], May 1, 1960; 89847 (Box 2, Item 960)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower, [1940s?]; 89846 (Box 4, Item 704)
  - Eisenstadt, [1950s?]; 89845 (Box 2, Item 964)
  - James Farrell, [1950s?]; 89844 (Box 2, Item 966)
  - Flynn [Board of Education?], [1950s?]; 89843 (Box 2, Item 961)
  - Carl J. Friedman of Howard University, 1946; 89842 (Box 1, Item 45)
  - Arthur Goldberg (Speaks -- Jewish Labor Committee), Jun 18, 1959; 89841 (Box 2, Item 967)
  - Gene Goldsmith, Oct 1, 1956; 89840 (Box 2, Item 963)
  - Paul Hall, Sep 23, 1953; 89839 (Box 4, Item 703)
  - [Copy shots of] George Harrison, President, Railway and Steamship Clerks, AFL, [1950s?]; 89838 (Box 2, Item 965)
  - Morris Iushewitz, Aug 1, 1950; 89837 (Box 2, Item 971)
  - WLIB [Radio], Arnold J. Jaffe, Mar 14, 1951; 89836 (Box 1, Item 652)
  - G. [George?] Jessel, [1950s?]; 89835 (Box 4, Item 705)
  - Arthur Kalster, Carnegie Hall Meeting, 1948; 89834 (Box 1, Item 46)
  - Dr. Karl [?], [1940s?]; 89833 (Box 4, Item 226)
  - Murray Koening, Nov 27, 1951; 89832 (Box 2, Item 968)
  - Political; La Guardia; Thomas Dewey; Alex [Rose]; Dewey and Luigi Antonini, [1930s?]; 89831 (Box 3, Item 1670)
  - Mort Lawrence, Gawdy 26 Bway, Oct 22, 1959; 89830 (Box 2, Item 970)
  - John L. Lewis; Anti-Nazi Meeting; Madison Square Garden; Note DD Johnson [David Dubinsky in corner], [1930s?]; 89829 (Box 3, Item 1674)
  - Jay Lovestone, 1934; 89828 (Box 1, Item 62)
  - [Jay Lovestone], [1940s?]; 89827 (Box 4, Item 227)
  - [Jay Lovestone], [1940s?]; 89826 (Box 4, Item 603)
  - J. J. [Jules?] Manson Portrait, Nov 23, 1956; 89825 (Box 2, Item 974)
  - J. J. [Jules?] Manson Portrai, Feb 17, 1957; 89824 (Box 2, Item 975)
  - Mr. Midgen Portrait, 1948; 89823 (Box 1, Item 44)
  - R. Mieblum [? Nieblux?], [1950s?]; 89822 (Box 2, Item 1008)
  - [Copy shots] Minkoff [?] -- Parents, [1950s?]; 89821 (Box 2, Item 1005)
  - Tom Mooney; New[bold?] Morris and T. M.; Antononi and T. M.; Welcome in [Madison Square Garden], [1930s?]; 89820 (Box 3, Item 1673)
  - John Mozen [Urzan?], [1950s?]; 89819 (Box 2, Item 1007)
  - Saby Nehama, Nov 9, 1950; 89818 (Box 2, Item 1006)
  - [A man (Oscar Newman?) accompanying a delegation of women and one child on a visit to Franklin D. Roosevelt's home, Hyde Park.], Sep 26, 1946; 89817 (Box 1, Item 65)
  - O'Donnel and Schwartz Accident, May 21, 1951; 89816 (Box 2, Item 1009)
  - Mayor William O'Dwyer, [Jun 1946); 89815 (Box 4, Item 544)
  - Harvey Olnick, Jun 1, 1949; 89814 (Box 1, Item 75)
  - Harvey Olnick Passport, [1950s?]; 89813 (Box 2, Item 1010)
  - Harvey Olnick, Feb 19, 1954; 89812 (Box 1, Item 728)
  - Alex W. -- L. Persands [?] [Exterior, man posed with two women], [1920s?]; 89811 (Box 1, Item 735)
  - Rose Pesotta Family, Sep 10, 1960; 89810 (Box 1, Item 729)
  - Bob Richardson, Jan 6, 1960; 89809 (Box 2, Item 1012)
  - Bob Richardson, Mar 17, 1960; 89808 (Box 2, Item 979)
  - Richard Riebo [?], [1950s?]; 89807 (Box 2, Item 1011)
  - Rogan, Larry, Textile [Textile Workers?] C.I.[O?], [1950s?]; 89806 (Box 2, Item 980)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt, [1940s?]; 89805 (Box 4, Item 543)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt, Portrait, undated (Box 6, Item 12057)
  - Samovodin [Samorodin?], Milton; Swearing in by [Judge] Matt Levy, Dec 29, 1951; 89804 (Box 2, Item 1001)
  - I. Scharfman at L.A.S. Affair[?], Jan 31, 1951; 89803 (Box 2, Item 981)
  - Schukin, Dave, [1960s?]; 89802 (Box 2, Item 982)
  - Seabury, [1950s?]; 89801 (Box 2, Item 983)
  - Bernard Seaman [Portaits], May 1, 1949; 89800 (Box 1, Item 74)
  - Seaman [Bernard Seaman's Daughter], [1950s?]; 89799 (Box 2, Item 987)
  - [Bernard Seaman with family], [1950s?]; 89798 (Box 2, Item 986)
  - [Bernard Seaman -- labor cartoonist -- Friend of Daniel Nilva's], [1950s?]; 89797 (Box 2, Item 984)
  - [Bernard] Seaman, [1950s?]; 89796 (Box 1, Item 730)
  - [Bernard Seaman Family], [1950s?]; 89795 (Box 1, Item 732)
  - [Bernard Seaman and Family], [1950s?]; 89794 (Box 1, Item 733)
  - [Bernard] Seaman, [Croton?] Meeting, Nov 25, 1950; 89793 (Box 1, Item 837)
  - Bernard Seaman, Feb 19, 1954; 89792 (Box 2, Item 985)
  - B. [Bernard] Seaman, Oct 1, 1954; 89791 (Box 1, Item 731)
  - [Copy shots] Dr. Ralph Sepsin, [1950s?]; 89790 (Box 2, Item 988)
  - Horatio [?] Seymour; Tammany Club; 364 W 23 St., Jan 31, 1952; 89789 (Box 2, Item 989)
  - Frances Smith, Jan 24, 1957; 89788 (Box 2, Item 990)
  - Dr. C. Snyder, Sep 12, 1957; 89787 (Box 2, Item 991)
  - Enrich [?] Springer. [Springer appears to be an African-American office-holder.] Judge Matt Levy Swearing in [? on Bible?], Oct 24, 1955; 89786 (Box 2, Item 972)
  - AFL-CIO Max Steinbock [Steinbach?], [1950s?]; 89785 (Box 2, Item 993)
  - Julie Steinberg, Dec 1, 1949; 89784 (Box 1, Item 64)
  - Lydia Tolstoy, Mar 20, 1951; 89783 (Box 2, Item 978)
  - Trare [sp?] Leimpkin, 1934; 89782 (Box 1, Item 77)
  - [New York City Mayor Wagner presents Miss Union Maid with a bouquet.], [1950s?]; 89781 (Box 2, Item 949)
  - Arthur K. Watson. VP -- IBM World Trade Corp, [1950s?]; 89780 (Box 2, Item 995)
  - E. Welsh [Labor], 1934; 89779 (Box 1, Item 63)
  - Edward K Welsh, 82 W. Montcalm, Detroit, Mich., Jan 11, 1957; 89778 (Box 2, Item 997)
  - Morton Wishengrad at typewriter, Jul 19, 1950; 89777 (Box 2, Item 996)
  - [Bertram D.] Wolfe, [1950s?]; 89776 (Box 2, Item 998)
  - [Bertram] D. Wolfe, 1934; 89775 (Box 1, Item 76)
  - Matthew Woll, [1950s?]; 89774 (Box 2, Item 1000)
  - [Matthew] Woll and Eric Jonston, [1950s?]; 89773 (Box 2, Item 999)
  - Lou Yagoda, Nov 24, 1959; 89772 (Box 1, Item 734)
  - Zimmerman, Charles, [1950s?]; 89771 (Box 2, Item 1002)
- Series VIII: Other Clients., 89679
  - Subseries VIII:A: American Veterans Committee., 89765
    - [American Veterans Committee]; Dinner Gross, Tyler and Goldsmith, Michael Straight; Belmont Plaza, Oct 12, 1956; 89769 (Box 2, Item 1013)